A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speech Transcripts, 1971-1974; 4; 4.4 Cubic Feet 12 document boxes
  - Remarks at the University of North Dakota, Grand Forks, 1973 November 26 (Box 83, Folder 994)
  - Remarks at the 18th District Republican Committee, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1973 November 26 (Box 83, Folder 995)
  - Remarks at the 5th District Republican Committee, Annual Dinner Minot, North Dakota, 1973 November 26 (Box 83, Folder 996)
  - Press Conference at 22 West 55th Street Office, New York City, 1973 November 27 (Box 83, Folder 997)
  - Remarks at the Citizen's Union Dinner Honoring Alton G. Marshall, New York City, 1973 November 27 (Box 83, Folder 998)
  - Remarks at the B'Nai B'rith Anti-Defamation League Dinner, New York City, 1973 November 29 (Box 83, Folder 999)
  - Remarks with Members of Congressional Delegation Holding the Fare, Washington DC, 1973 November 30 (Box 83, Folder 1000)
  - News Conference at the Morning Session of the National Comm. On Critical Choices for America, New York City, 1973 December 4 (Box 83, Folder 1001)
  - Press Conference at 22nd West 55th Street Office, New York City, 1973 December 5 (Box 83, Folder 1002)
  - Remarks at 1973 Southern Republican Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, 1973 December 7 (Box 83, Folder 1003)
  - Remarks at the Institute of Adult Jewish Studies, New York City, 1973 December 10 (Box 83, Folder 1004)
  - Press Questions following Announcement of Resignation, Red Room, State Capital, Albany, NY, 1973 December 11 (Box 84, Folder 1005)
  - Press Conference before "Man of Conscience" Award Dinner, New York City, 1973 December 11 (Box 84, Folder 1006)
  - Remarks at "Meet the Press", New York City, 1973 December 16 (Box 84, Folder 1007)
  - Speech on Oil, Denver Colorado, 1974 January 31 (Box 84, Folder 1008)
  - Remarks at Bond Club of New York, 1974 February 1 (Box 84, Folder 1009)
  - Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller on Newsmakers, Channel 13 T.V. Bill Taylor, Rockford, Illinois, 1974 February 9 (Box 84, Folder 1010)
  - Remarks at Rockford, Illinois, 1974 February 9 (Box 84, Folder 1011)
  - Remarks at Congressman John Anderson Dinner, Rockton, Illinois, 1974 February 9 (Box 84, Folder 1012)
  - Press Conference at 30 Rockefeller Plaza, New York City, 1974 February 11 (Box 84, Folder 1013)
  - Remarks at the American College of Cardiology, New York City, 1974 February 11 (Box 84, Folder 1014)
  - Remarks at the Republican State Central Comm. Dinner, Rapid City. South Dakota, 1974 February 12 (Box 84, Folder 1015)
  - Remarks at Press Conference in Mitchell, South Dakota, 1974 February 12 (Box 84, Folder 1016)
  - Remarks at Rapid City, South Dakota, 1974 February 12 (Box 84, Folder 1017)
  - Press Conference of Nelson A. Rockefeller at Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1974 February 12 (Box 84, Folder 1018)
  - Remarks Fund Raising Luncheon for Senator Robert Dole, Topeka, Kansas, 1974 February 13 (Box 84, Folder 1019)
  - Remarks in Dallas, Texas, 1974 February 21 (Box 84, Folder 1020)
  - Interview of Nelson A. Rockefeller on the Murphy Martin Show, Dallas, Texas, 1974 February 21 (Box 84, Folder 1021)
  - Remarks at the University - Oral History Lyndon B. Johnson, Austin, Texas, 1974 February 21 (Box 84, Folder 1022)
  - Remarks at Dallas Council on World Affairs, Dallas, Texas, 1974 February 22 (Box 84, Folder 1023)
  - Remarks of Nelson A. Rockefeller in Billings, Montana, 1974 February 28 (Box 84, Folder 1024)
  - Remarks at Seaside, Oregon (Dorchester Conference), 1974 March 1 (Box 84, Folder 1025)
  - T.V. Taping, The McKay Show, Seaside, Oregon, 1974 March 1 (Box 84, Folder 1026)
  - Remarks at the Testimonial Dinner for Senator Javits, New York City, 1974 March 4 (Box 84, Folder 1027)
  - Remarks at Regents Conference-Critical Choices, New York City, 1974 March 5 (Box 84, Folder 1028)
  - Remarks at Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1974 March 7 (Box 84, Folder 1029)
  - Remarks at Sarasota, Florida, 1974 March 8 (Box 84, Folder 1030)
  - Remarks at Boston, Massachusetts, 1974 March 13 (Box 85, Folder 1031)
  - Remarks at Odyssey House, "Man of the Year Award" Dinner, New York City, 1974 March 14 (Box 85, Folder 1032)
  - Remarks at Midwest Republican Leadership Conference, Chicago, Illinois, 1974 March 30 (Box 85, Folder 1033)
  - Remarks in Miami, Florida, 1974 April 3 (Box 85, Folder 1034)
  - Remarks at National Comm. On Water Quality, Washington DC, 1974 April 5 (Box 85, Folder 1035)
  - News Conference in Lincoln, Nebraska, 1974 April 6 (Box 85, Folder 1036)
  - Remarks at the Wharton Graduate Business School Club Award Dinner, New York City, 1974 April 16 (Box 85, Folder 1037)
  - Remarks at the American Society of Magazine Editors, New York City, 1974 April 23 (Box 85, Folder 1038)
  - Remarks at Annual Conference at the American Society for Public Administration, Syracuse, NY, 1973 May 6 (Box 85, Folder 1039)
  - Remarks in Kansas City, Missouri, 1974 May 9 (Box 85, Folder 1040)
  - Press Conference in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1974 May 9 (Box 85, Folder 1041)
  - Remarks at the Jackson County Republican Comm. Dinner, Kansas City, 1974 May 9 (Box 85, Folder 1042)
  - Remarks at Tribute to Winthrop Rockefeller, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1974 May 10 (Box 85, Folder 1043)
  - Remarks at the New York State Council of the Arts Luncheon, Buffalo, NY, 1974 May 16 (Box 85, Folder 1044)
  - Remarks at Tenth Annual Republican Legislative Dinner, Lansing, Michigan, 1974 May 22 (Box 85, Folder 1045)
  - Remarks at the Eternal Light Program on NBC, New York City, 1974 May 26 (Box 85, Folder 1046)
  - Remarks at the Association for a Better New York, New York City, 1974 May 31 (Box 85, Folder 1047)
  - Remarks at the Edison Electric Institute, New York City, 1974 June 5 (Box 85, Folder 1048)
  - Remarks at the Taft School, Watertown, Connecticut, 1974 June 10 (Box 85, Folder 1049)
  - Remarks at the Office and Professional Employees Union Convention, Remarks Miami, Florida, 1974 June 11 (Box 85, Folder 1050)
  - Remarks at the Republican State Convention, Uniondale, NY, 1974 June 12 (Box 85, Folder 1051)
  - Remarks at the Republican State Comm. Annual Dinner, New York City, 1974 June 13 (Box 85, Folder 1052)
  - Remarks at the Cuyahoga-Lake Republican Finance Comm. Fund-Raising Dinner, Cleveland, Ohio, 1974 June 14 (Box 85, Folder 1053)
  - Remarks at the Wyoming Republican State Comm. Fund-Raising Dinner, Gillette, Wyoming, 1974 June 18 (Box 86, Folder 1054)
  - Remarks at the Republican Fund-Raising Luncheon, Spokane, Washington, 1974 June 19 (Box 86, Folder 1055)
  - Remarks at the Republican Fund-Raising Barbeque, Everett, Washington, 1974 June 19 (Box 86, Folder 1056)
  - Announcement of Mrs. Helen A. Kitchen as African Studies Director, Comm. On Critical Choices for Americans, 1974 July 23 (Box 86, Folder 1057)
  - Remarks at the International Convention of the National Newspaper Association, Toronto, Canada, 1974 July 26 (Box 86, Folder 1058)
  - Remarks at the Maine Republican State Comm. Dinner, Bangor, Maine, 1974 August 9 (Box 86, Folder 1059)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller at Chicago, Illinois, 1974 August 11 (Box 86, Folder 1060)
  - Remarks by Nelson A. Rockefeller at the White House, Washington DC, 1974 August 20 (Box 86, Folder 1061)
  - Remarks at the Jim Nugent for Governor Fund-Raising Dinner, Newport, Rhode Island, 1974 August 21 (Box 86, Folder 1062)
  - Remarks at the Department of State Radio and T.V. News Briefing, Washington DC, 1974 August 22 (Box 86, Folder 1063)
  - Press Conference at Seal Harbor, Maine, 1974 August 23 (Box 86, Folder 1064)
  - Press Questions for Nelson A. Rockefeller, Washington. DC, 1974 August 28 (Box 86, Folder 1065)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller Arriving at Westchester Airport, 1974 August 31 (Box 86, Folder 1066)
  - News Conference at 55 Street Office, New York City, 1974 September 3 (Box 86, Folder 1067)
  - Commission on Critical Choices for the Americas, Photo/Film Coverage of Meeting, New York City, 1974 September 5 (Box 86, Folder 1068)
  - Sidewalk Conference of Nelson A. Rockefeller, New York City, 1974 September 9 (Box 86, Folder 1069)
  - Remarks before Religious Zionists of America, 1974 September 12 (Box 86, Folder 1070)
  - Vice President Senate Confirmation Hearing, Index, 1974 September 22-27 (Box 86, Folder 1071)
  - Vice President Senate Confirmation Testimony, Reading Copy, 1974 September 21 (Box 86, Folder 1072)
  - Vice President Senate Confirmation Testimony, Original Copy, 1974 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1073)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Statement before Senate Rules Committee, Vice President Senate Confirmation Hearing, 1974 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1074)
  - Vice President Senate Confirmation Hearing, Statement of Financial Assets, 1974 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1075)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, Volume 1, 1974 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1076)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, Volume 2, 1974 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1077)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, Volume 1, 1974 September 24 (Box 87, Folder 1078)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, Volume 2, 1974 September 24 (Box 87, Folder 1079)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, 1974 September 25 (Box 87, Folder 1080)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings, 1974 September 26 (Box 88, Folder 1081)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings. Working Papers, Background Notes., 1974 September 23-27 (Box 88, Folder 1082)
  - Vice President Testimony, Proceedings. Working Papers, "Wild Pages.", 1974 September 21 (Box 88, Folder 1083)
  - Remarks at Bringham Young University, Utah, 1974 October 2 (Box 88, Folder 1084)
  - Press Questions at 22 West 55th Street, New York City, 1974 October 8 (Box 88, Folder 1085)
  - Remarks at Sidewalk Press Interview-Confirmation Hearings, 1974 October 15 (Box 88, Folder 1086)
  - Press Conference, Confirmation Hearings, 1974 October 16 (Box 88, Folder 1087)
  - Interview for German T.V. by Margaret Dvenser, Sweites Deutsches Fernsehen, 1974 October 16 (Box 88, Folder 1088)
  - News Conference of Nelson A. Rockefeller held at 22 West 55th Street, New York City, 1974 October 17 (Box 88, Folder 1089)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Federal and Gift Tax Returns, Memorandum (CLOSED FOLDER), 1974 October 18 (Box 88, Folder 1090)
  - Press Questions, Nelson A. Rockefeller Entering Hospital, New York City, 1974 October 21 (Box 88, Folder 1091)
  - Remarks at Sidewalk Interview, 22 West 55th Street, New York City, 1974 October 22 (Box 88, Folder 1092)
  - Statement, Release of Mrs. Rockefeller from Memorial Sloan Kettering Hospital, New York City, 1974 October 24 (Box 88, Folder 1093)
  - Letter from Nelson A. Rockefeller to Howard Cannon and Peter Rodino with List of Loans, 1957-1974 (Box 88, Folder 1094)
  - Statement to the Press by Hugh Morrow, RE: Jack Nelson Story in the Los Angeles Times, 1974 November 1 (Box 88, Folder 1095)
  - Statement for Ralph Blumenthal, New York Times, NY, 1974 November 8 (Box 88, Folder 1096)
  - Index on Senate Confirmation Hearings 1, 1974 November 13-15 (Box 88, Folder 1097)
  - Index on Senate Confirmation Hearings 2, 1974 November 13-15 (Box 88, Folder 1098)
  - Statement of Nelson A. Rockefeller Senate Committee on Rules and Administration, 1974 November 13 (Box 89, Folder 1099)
  - Text Prepared for Committee on Rules and Administration, United States Senate, 1974 November 13 (Box 89, Folder 1100)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Statement Reopening of Senate Hearings, 1975 November 13 (Box 89, Folder 1101)
  - Laurence S. Rockefeller's Statement Before the Committee on Rules and Administration, United State Senate, 1974 November 15 (Box 89, Folder 1102)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Statement House Judiciary Committee, 1974 November 21 (Box 89, Folder 1103)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Statement House Judiciary Committee, 1974 November 21 (Box 89, Folder 1104)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller on Arrival at Page National Airport, Washington DC, 1974 November 21 (Box 89, Folder 1105)
  - Press Questions on Mrs. Rockefeller's Arrival at Memorial Hospital, New York City, 1974 November 24 (Box 89, Folder 1106)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller Arriving at Memorial Hospital, New York City, 1974 November 25 (Box 89, Folder 1107)
  - Statement by J. Richardson Dilworth before the Committee on the Judiciary of the House of Representatives, 1974 December 3 (Box 89, Folder 1108)
  - Statement by Laurance S. Rockefeller Before the Committee on the Judiciary of the House of Representatives, 1974 December 3 (Box 89, Folder 1109)
  - Nomination of Nelson A. Rockefeller to be Vice President of the Unites States, 1974 December 3 (Box 89, Folder 1110)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller House of Representatives Testimony, 1974 December 5 (Box 90, Folder 1111)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller Following Confirmation, New York City, 1994 December 10 (Box 90, Folder 1112)
  - Press Questions of Nelson A. Rockefeller Following Receipt of Phone Call from Representative McClory, New York City, 1974 December 12 (Box 90, Folder 1113)
  - Press Questions of Israeli Foreign Minister Allon, New York City, 1974 December 12 (Box 90, Folder 1114)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Swearing in as Vice President, 1974 December 19 (Box 90, Folder 1115)
- Vice Presidential Press Releases, 1975-1976; 5; 1.6 Cubic Feet 5 document boxes
  This collection of press releases covers the two years Rockefeller served as U.S. Vice President.
  - 1975 January (Box 90, Folder 1116)
  - 1975 February (Box 90, Folder 1117)
  - 1975 March (Box 90, Folder 1118)
  - 1975 April (Box 90, Folder 1119)
  - 1975 May (Box 90, Folder 1120)
  - 1975 June (Box 90, Folder 1121)
  - 1975 July (Box 90, Folder 1122)
  - 1975 August (Box 90, Folder 1123)
  - 1975 September (Box 91, Folder 1124)
  - 1975 October 1-16 (Box 91, Folder 1125)
  - 1975 October 21-31 (Box 91, Folder 1126)
  - 1975 November (Box 91, Folder 1127)
  - 1975 December (Box 91, Folder 1128)
  - Statement of Nelson A. Rockefeller before the New York State Moreland Act Commission on the Urban Development Corporporation (UDC), 1975 December 3 (Box 91, Folder 1129)
  - "The Future of Freedom," Vice President's Bicentennial Series, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 1130)
  - 1976 January (Box 92, Folder 1131)
  - 1976 February (Box 92, Folder 1132)
  - 1976 March 4-12 (Box 92, Folder 1133)
  - 1976 March 16-31 (Box 92, Folder 1134)
  - 1976 April 2-12 (Box 92, Folder 1135)
  - 1976 April 14-30 (Box 92, Folder 1136)
  - 1976 May 4-14 (Box 92, Folder 1137)
  - 1977 May 14-30 (Box 92, Folder 1138)
  - 1976 June (Box 93, Folder 1139)
  - 1976 July (Box 93, Folder 1140)
  - 1976 August (Box 93, Folder 1141)
  - 1976 September 14-22 (Box 93, Folder 1142)
  - 1976 September 28-29 (Box 93, Folder 1143)
  - 1976 October 2-12 (Box 93, Folder 1144)
  - 1976 October 13-14 (Box 93, Folder 1145)
  - 1976 October 18-19 (Box 94, Folder 1146)
  - 1976 October 20-27 (Box 94, Folder 1147)
  - 1976 November (Box 94, Folder 1148)
  - 1976 December (Box 94, Folder 1149)
- Subject Files, 1955-1974; 6; 4 Cubic Feet 11 document boxes
  This miscellaneous collection of "end files" contains material similar to what is found in the General Files and Campaign Files subseries.
  - The Academy in Turmoil: Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, Albany, NY, 1970 February 1 (Box 94, Folder 1150)
  - The Academy or Battleground: Third Report of the Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, Albany, NY, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 1151)
  - Art Exhibitions at Museum of Primitive Art, 1968 March 1-1969 August 13 (Box 94, Folder 1152)
  - Basic Nelson Rockefeller Record-State, National, Foreign, 1968 May 28-1970 January 31 (Box 95, Folder 1153)
  - Budget Leaflet, 1969 January 31-May 6 (Box 95, Folder 1154)
  - Campaign 1970: Miscellaneous, 1970 January 27-August 26 (Box 95, Folder 1155)
  - Campaign 1970: National Issues, Rockefeller Task Force, 1970 April 27-July 21 (Box 95, Folder 1156)
  - Campaign 1970: Rockefeller Record up to 1970, Aging to Education, 1970 May (Box 95, Folder 1157)
  - Campaign 1970: Rockefeller Record up to 1970, Environment to Health, 1970 May (Box 95, Folder 1158)
  - Campaign 1970: Rockefeller Record up to 1970, Housing to Youth, 1970 May (Box 95, Folder 1159)
  - Campaign 1970: Political Data, Program Data (Box 96, Folder 1160)
  - Campaign 1970: Political Data, Program Data (Box 96, Folder 1161)
  - Campaign 1972: Judge Charles D. Breitel Campaign, 1973 July 24-October 20 (Box 96, Folder 1162)
  - Campaign 1972: Convention-Miami, 1972 August 21 (Box 96, Folder 1163)
  - Campaign 1972: Convention-Miami, Background Material, 1972 August 15-18 (Box 96, Folder 1164)
  - Campaign 1972: Convention-Miami, Background Material, 1972 July 13-26 (Box 96, Folder 1165)
  - Campaign 1972: Democrats Convention, 1972 July 11-October 31 (Box 96, Folder 1166)
  - Campaign 1972: Democrats Convention, 1972 June 20-October 5 (Box 96, Folder 1167)
  - Campaign 1972: New York State: 1972 Environmental Board Coalition, 1972 August 3-October 3 (Box 97, Folder 1168)
  - Campaign 1972: Nixon, Richard Nominating Speech, 1972 August 22 (Box 97, Folder 1169)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, Miscellaneous, 1971 August 8-September 12 (Box 97, Folder 1170)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, National, 1972 October 2-November 6 (Box 97, Folder 1171)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, National, 1972 June 13-September 28 (Box 97, Folder 1172)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, National, 1971 January 26-1972 May 30 (Box 97, Folder 1173)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, New York State Campaign for Nixon, 1972 July 17-September 12 (Box 97, Folder 1174)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, Nominating Speech, Working Papers, 1972 August 23 (Box 97, Folder 1175)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, National, Politics, Speeches-National, 1972 May 12-November 3 (Box 97, Folder 1176)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics-Statistics, Margins of Election of Governor's of New York State, 1918-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1177)
  - Campaign 1972: Politics, Vergari-Peyser Campaign, Westchester, NY, 1972 June 20-October 16 (Box 98, Folder 1178)
  - Campaign 1973: Mayoralty, 1972 December 13-1973 April 26 (Box 98, Folder 1179)
  - Campaign 1973: Transportation Bond Issue, 1973 September 4-November 9 (Box 98, Folder 1180)
  - Campaign 1973: Transportation Bond Issue, 1973 July 15-August 14 (Box 98, Folder 1181)
  - Campaign, Speeches and Correspondence, 1970 March 26-August 28 (Box 98, Folder 1182)
  - Campaign, Strategy - Political, 1969 November 25-1970 October 21 (Box 98, Folder 1183)
  - Campaign, Tax Dollars-Case Histories, 1970 April 16-May 8 (Box 98, Folder 1184)
  - Campaign, Tax Dollars-Case Histories, 1970 April 1-3 (Box 98, Folder 1185)
  - Campaign, Tax Dollars-Case Histories, 1970 March 20-31 (Box 98, Folder 1186)
  - Campaign, Tax Dollars-Case Histories, 1970 January 19-March 17 (Box 98, Folder 1187)
  - Campaign, Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1970 July 6-October 22 (Box 99, Folder 1188)
  - Campaign, Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1970 April 8-June 30 (Box 99, Folder 1189)
  - Campaign, Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1969 December 4-March 30 (Box 99, Folder 1190)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Meeting Correspondence, 1969 June 12-1970 November 2 (Box 99, Folder 1191)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals, 1969 Rockefeller Commission Program (Box 99, Folder 1192)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals, 1970 Advertizing Campaign Plan, 1970 June (Box 99, Folder 1193)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals, A Qualitative Study of Voter's Attitudes in New York State, 1970 April (Box 99, Folder 1194)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals-Surveys, New York Republican State Commission, 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 99, Folder 1195)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals, Proposals for 1969 Rockefeller Communications Program (Box 99, Folder 1196)
  - Campaign, Tinker, Jack, Proposals, Research Proposals: Nelson Rockefeller for Governor Campaign, 1970 February 1 (Box 99, Folder 1197)
  - Campaign, Transportation Public Relations, 1970 January 23-October 16 (Box 99, Folder 1198)
  - Campaign, "Weeklies with Rockefeller", 1970 May 1-October 22 (Box 100, Folder 1199)
  - Campaign, Westchester County, Nin Jones, 1970 May 12-October 30 (Box 100, Folder 1200)
  - Campaign, Wilson, Malcolm, 1970 July 15-October 27 (Box 100, Folder 1201)
  - Campaign, Dr. Winkler. "5 Minute TV. Script" (Background Material), 1970 October (Box 100, Folder 1202)
  - Campaign, Youth, 1970 September 8-11 (Box 100, Folder 1203)
  - Campaign, Youth College Press Conference, 1970 February 23-June 15 (Box 100, Folder 1204)
  - Campaign, Women, 1970 August 20-October 9 (Box 100, Folder 1205)
  - Clippings, Politics, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 1206)
  - Fiscal Problems, Other States, 1969 April-May (Box 100, Folder 1207)
  - Latin American Trip, Press Arrangements, 1969 March 21-May 15 (Box 100, Folder 1208)
  - Latin American Trip, Press Releases, and Clippings, 1969 March 12-May 26 (Box 100, Folder 1209)
  - Latin American Trip, Press Releases and Clippings, 1969 June 4-December 12 (Box 100, Folder 1210)
  - Latin American Trip, Report, 1970 January 2-April 16 (Box 101, Folder 1211)
  - Latin American Trip, Report, Distribution of Spanish Report, 1970 December 1-1971 January 14 (Box 101, Folder 1212)
  - Nelson Rockefeller Policy Statements, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 1213)
  - Nelson Rockefeller Town Meeting, Film 1969, 1969 March 1-August 5 (Box 101, Folder 1214)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Background Material, 1955 December 5-1974 December 22 (Box 101, Folder 1215)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Background Material, 1955 October 16-November 22 (Box 101, Folder 1216)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Background Material, 1955 October 3-14 (Box 101, Folder 1217)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Background Material, 1955 August 1-September 25 (Box 102, Folder 1218)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Background Material, 1955 June 30-28 (Box 102, Folder 1219)
  - Open Skies - Quantico Files, Declassification, 1974 January 21-July 30 (Box 102, Folder 1220)
  - Polls: Action for Transportation in New York State, Inc., 1971 September (Box 102, Folder 1221)
  - Polls: Anti-Pollution Bond Issue (Pure Water), 1971 December 29-1972 April 25 (Box 102, Folder 1222)
  - Polls: Candidates for Westchester County Executive, 1973 February (Box 102, Folder 1223)
  - Polls: Final Report on Campaign Polling in New York, 1970 November 23 (Box 102, Folder 1224)
  - Polls: Data Gubernatorial Candidates (Lloyd Free), 1970 July-August (Box 102, Folder 1225)
  - Polls: Lloyd Free Correspondence, 1969 March 13-1970 September 30 (Box 102, Folder 1226)
  - Polls: General Correspondence and Memos, 1969 October 9-1970 October 25 (Box 103, Folder 1227)
  - Polls: Sam Lubell Correspondence, 1970 August 18-October 22 (Box 103, Folder 1228)
  - Polls: New York State Opinion Potential Candidates for United States Senator, 1970 February (Box 103, Folder 1229)
  - Polls: New York State Opinion on Several Key Issues, 1969 June (Box 103, Folder 1230)
  - Polls: Political Opinion in New York State, 1970 April (Box 103, Folder 1231)
  - Polls: Popularity of Possible Candidates for Mayor of New York City, 1973 February 28 (Box 103, Folder 1232)
  - Polls: Public Attitudes Affecting the Rockefeller Candidacy, 1970 September (Box 103, Folder 1233)
  - Polls: Public Attitudes on Handling Various Problems Confronting New York State, 1970 December (Box 103, Folder 1234)
  - Polls: Public Attitudes Towards New York State Spending, (Education), 1969 December (Box 103, Folder 1235)
  - Polls: Public Attitudes About the Subway, 1970 August 31 (Box 103, Folder 1236)
  - Polls: Public Attitudes Towards Selected Issues and Personalities, 1972 December-1973 January (Box 104, Folder 1237)
  - Polls: Public Reaction to the Rockefeller Proposed Crack-Down on Drug Pushers, 1973 February 20 (Box 104, Folder 1238)